# Brian Dumoulin

10730 E 26th Ave, Aurora, CO 🏫

603.479.3252

bmdumoulin10@gmail.com 💟

LinkedIn in

GitHub

Obtain a position as a full-stack developer utilizing 2+ years of development experience to become a key contributor of a development team. Continue to learn new strategies, languages, and techniques to grow and fine-tune the craft.

#### Skills

- JavaScript / Related Libraries & Frameworks
- HTML
- CSS / Related Frameworks
- PHP
- Free Marker
- JSON
- ISO 20022 XML Payment File Formatting
- Leadership, Training, & Teamwork

- Functional & Object Oriented Programming
- Waterfall & Agile Methodologies
- Version Control (Git / TFS)
- Web Hosting (Digital Ocean)
- REST APIs & Integrations
- CLI
- ERP
- CRM

#### **Experience**

AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT

### Sr. Web Application Developer / RSM US, LLP, Denver CO

Use JavaScript and the SuiteScript API to <u>design</u> and <u>develop</u> robust integrations and customizations to the NetSuite ERP. Lead development teams and train new team members.

**DECEMBER 2016 - JULY 2018** 

### Web Application Developer / RSM US, LLP, Denver CO

Use JavaScript and the SuiteScript API to develop robust integrations and customizations to the NetSuite ERP.

SEPTEMBER 2016 - DECEMBER 2016

### **Instructor / Coding With Kids, Denver CO**

Teach elementary school kids basic coding concepts using Scratch.

#### **Education**

JULY 2016

## Full Stack JavaScript Development / RefactorU, Boulder CO

400+ hours of hands on web development using the JavaScript based MEAN Stack.

MAY 2009

# Sociology / University of New Hampshire, Durham NH

Minor, Business Administration